Finding Aid for the Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo, 2008
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo, 2008
Mus. Arc. 39
Haupt, Irene
10 CD-ROMS (234 digital images in tiff format)
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library 112 Baird Hall Buffalo, New York 14260-4750 United States Phone: 716 645-2924 Fax: 716 645-3906
Contains 234 digital images (tiff files) of musicians who participated in the June in Buffalo Festival 2008 at the University at Buffalo.
Administrative Information
Terms of Access
Materials can be examined by qualified researchers in the Music Library during hours of operation during which Music Librarians are present. In order to insure access, researchers are advised to contact the Music Library in advance of visits.
Acquisition Information
Purchased from Irene Haupt, 2008.
Accruals and Additions
No further accruals are expected to this collection.
Alternate Forms
145 images from the June in Buffalo 2008 collection are included in the University at Buffalo Libraries Digital Collections.
Biographical Note
Irene Haupt, a graduate of the State University of New York at Buffalo, has been documenting the Buffalo arts scene through her photography since 1976. During that time she has worked for, or with, some of the most notable institutions in Buffalo, including the Irish Classical Theatre, Studio Arena Theater, the Kavinoky Theatre, the Buffalo Philharmonic Orchestra, the Theatre of Youth, the Albright-Knox Art Gallery, and the State University of New York at Buffalo. In addition to her specialty of theater photography, Irene Haupt has also devoted much of her career to the photography of musicians and musical events. Most notable is her documentation of the contemporary music scene in Buffalo, including coverage of the University at Buffalo's June in Buffalo festival of new music, 1982-1987, and 2000 to the present. Over the course of those years, she has created a visual record that contains images of some of the most significant composers and performers of the last quarter century. The list of names is impressive: Aaron Copland, Morton Feldman, Leo Smit, Virgil Thomson, Steve Reich, Ralph Shapey, Henry Brant, Earle Brown, Ursula Oppens, Jan Williams, Lukas Foss, Philip Glass, Otto Luening, Conlon Nancarrow, Ernst Krenek, Larry Austin, Lejaren Hiller, Elliott Carter, Milton Babbitt, John Cage, Charles Wuorinen, Jacob Druckman, and Yvar Mikhashoff, among others.
The June in Buffalo festival of contemporary music was begun at the University at Buffalo in 1975 by composer Morton Feldman. He directed the festival 1975-1978 and in 1980. The festival was dormant from 1981 through 1985. David Felder revived the festival in 1986 and has been its director since that time.
Scope and Content Note
The collection of Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2008 contains 234 images of participants in the festival for 2008. The list of musicians includes David Felder, Ben Thigpen, Charles Dodge, James Avery, Stefan Haussler, Cort Lippe, Nicholas Isherwood, Gerald Pape, Miller Puckette, Morton Subotnick, Roberto Morales, Daniel Hoffmann, Ensemble for Intuitive Music, Rin Ozaki, Eun Ju Kim, Tom Kolor, Hans Tutschku, and Stephen Gosling.
Arrangement
Ten series, one for each CD-ROM. Series titles are either transciptions of markings on the CD-ROMS or created based on principle content.
I. CD-ROM 1. David Felder '08
II. CD-ROM 2. Capricorn
III. CD-ROM 3. June in Buffalo '08
IV. CD-ROM 4. Roberto Morales (supplied)
V. CD-ROM 5. Morton Subotnick (supplied)
VI. CD-ROM 6. Miller Puckette (supplied)
VII. CD-ROM 7. Ben Thigpen (supplied)
VIII. CD-ROM 8. Charles Dodge
IX. CD-ROM 9. James Avery
X. CD-ROM 10. Ensemble for Intuition [sic] Musik '08
Container List
- David Felder '08, June 2008, I.; 1 CD-ROM (24 image files in TIFF format)
  Files are numerically arranged by intermediate, assigned file names. Original file names are included for reference.
  - Nicholas Isherwood performing David Felder's work, Shemayin, in front of the projection of film by Elliot Caplan, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: =David Felder Shemayin voice Nicholas Isherwood=.tif (Image-file cd01-01)
  - Nicholas Isherwood performing David Felder's work, Shemayin, in front of the projection of film by Elliot Caplan, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Chashmal composer David Felder.tif (Image-file cd01-02)
  - Nicholas Isherwood performing David Felder's work, Shemayin, in front of the projection of film by Elliot Caplan, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Chashmal voice Nicholas Isherwood.tif (Image-file cd01-03)
  - Nicholas Isherwood performing David Felder's work, Shemayin, in front of the projection of film by Elliot Caplan, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: David Felder Chashmal voice Nicholas Isherwood=.tif (Image-file cd01-04)
  - Nicholas Isherwood performing David Felder's work, Shemayin, in front of the projection of film by Elliot Caplan, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: David Felder Shemayim voice Nicholas Isherwood..tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200801-05 (Image-file cd01-05)
  - Nicholas Isherwood performing David Felder's work, Shemayin, in front of the projection of film by Elliot Caplan, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: David Felder Shemayin voice Nicholas Isherwood=..tif (Image-file cd01-06)
  - Nicholas Isherwood performing David Felder's work, Shemayin, in front of the projection of film by Elliot Caplan, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: David Felder Shemayin voice Nicholas--.tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200801-07 (Image-file cd01-07)
  - Nicholas Isherwood performing David Felder's work, Shemayin, in front of the projection of film by Elliot Caplan, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: JIB 08 019.tif (Image-file cd01-08)
  - Nicholas Isherwood performing David Felder's work, Shemayin, in front of the projection of film by Elliot Caplan, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: JIB 08 022.tif (Image-file cd01-09)
  - Nicholas Isherwood performing David Felder's work, Shemayin, in front of the projection of film by Elliot Caplan, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: JIB 08 028.tif (Image-file cd01-10)
  - Nicholas Isherwood performing David Felder's work, Shemayin, in front of the projection of film by Elliot Caplan, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: JIB 08 030.tif (Image-file cd01-11)
  - Nicholas Isherwood performing David Felder's work, Shemayin, in front of the projection of film by Elliot Caplan, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: JIB 08 031.tif (Image-file cd01-12)
  - Nicholas Isherwood performing David Felder's work, Shemayin, in front of the projection of film by Elliot Caplan, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: JIB 08 035.tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200801-13 (Image-file cd01-13)
  - Nicholas Isherwood performing David Felder's work, Shemayin, in front of the projection of film by Elliot Caplan, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: JIB 08 042.tif (Image-file cd01-14)
  - Nicholas Isherwood performing David Felder's work, Shemayin, in front of the projection of film by Elliot Caplan, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: JIB 08 044.tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200801-15 (Image-file cd01-15)
  - Nicholas Isherwood performing David Felder's work, Shemayin, in front of the projection of film by Elliot Caplan, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: JIB 08 050.tif (Image-file cd01-16)
  - Nicholas Isherwood performing David Felder's work, Shemayin, in front of the projection of film by Elliot Caplan, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: JIB 08 051.tif (Image-file cd01-17)
  - Nicholas Isherwood performing David Felder's work, Shemayin, in front of the projection of film by Elliot Caplan, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: JIB 08 066.tif (Image-file cd01-18)
  - Nicholas Isherwood performing David Felder's work, Shemayin, in front of the projection of film by Elliot Caplan, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: JIB 08.tif (Image-file cd01-19)
  - Nicholas Isherwood performing David Felder's work, Shemayin, in front of the projection of film by Elliot Caplan, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Nicholas Isherwood in Chasmal by David Felder.tif (Image-file cd01-20)
  - Nicholas Isherwood performing David Felder's work, Shemayin, in front of the projection of film by Elliot Caplan, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Nicolas Isherwood.tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200801-21 (Image-file cd01-21)
  - Nicholas Isherwood performing David Felder's work, Shemayin, in front of the projection of film by Elliot Caplan, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Shemayin by David Felder voice Nicholas Isherwood=-.tif (Image-file cd01-22)
  - Nicholas Isherwood performing David Felder's work, Shemayin, in front of the projection of film by Elliot Caplan, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Shemayin-.tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200801-23 (Image-file cd01-23)
  - Nicholas Isherwood performing David Felder's work, Shemayin, in front of the projection of film by Elliot Caplan, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Voice Nicholas Isherwood Shemayin by David Felder.tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200801-24 (Image-file cd01-24)
- Capricorn, June 2008, II.; 1 CD-ROM (10 image files in TIFF format)
  Images of singer Nicholas Isherwood during rehearsal of David Felder's composition, Capricorn.
  - Nicholas Isherwood performing Karlheinz Stockhausen's, Capricorn, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: 132.tif (Image-file cd02-01)
  - Nicholas Isherwood performing Karlheinz Stockhausen's, Capricorn, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: 132==.tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200802-02 (Image-file cd02-02)
  - Nicholas Isherwood performing Karlheinz Stockhausen's, Capricorn, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: 133.tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200802-03 (Image-file cd02-03)
  - Nicholas Isherwood performing Karlheinz Stockhausen's, Capricorn, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Capricorn by STOCKHAUSEN.tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200802-04 (Image-file cd02-04)
  - Nicholas Isherwood performing Karlheinz Stockhausen's, Capricorn, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Capricorrn slee hall.tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200802-05 (Image-file cd02-05)
  - Nicholas Isherwood performing Karlheinz Stockhausen's, Capricorn, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Isherwood.tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200802-06 (Image-file cd02-06)
  - Nicholas Isherwood performing Karlheinz Stockhausen's, Capricorn, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Isherwood=.tif (Image-file cd02-07)
  - Nicholas Isherwood performing Karlheinz Stockhausen's, Capricorn, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Nicholas Isherwood rehearsing.tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200802-08 (Image-file cd02-08)
  - Nicholas Isherwood performing Karlheinz Stockhausen's, Capricorn, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Stockhausen Capricorn-=.tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200802-09 (Image-file cd02-09)
  - Nicholas Isherwood performing Karlheinz Stockhausen's, Capricorn, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Stockhausen Capricorn-=======.tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200802-10 (Image-file cd02-10)
- June in Buffalo '08, June 2008, III.; 1 CD-ROM (32 image files in TIFF format)
  - Percussionist Tom Kolor, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: -Tom Kolor, percussion.tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200803-01 (Image-file cd03-01)
  - Composer Cort Lippe, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Composer Cort Lippe.tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200803-02 (Image-file cd03-02)
  - Composers Cort Lippe and Roberto Morales with conductor James Avery, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: composer Cort Lippe, Morales conductor James Avery at rehear.tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200803-03 (Image-file cd03-03)
  - Composer Gerard Pape, guitarist Magnus Andersson, and bass Nicholas Isherwood, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: composer Gerard Pape Magnus Andersson, guitar- Nicholas Ishe.tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200803-04 (Image-file cd03-04)
  - Composer Cort Lippe at masterclass with June in Buffalo students, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Cort Lippe masterclass.tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200803-05 (Image-file cd03-05)
  - Composer David Felder with bass Nicholas Isherwood and composer Miller Puckette, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: David Felder Isherwood Miller Puckette.tif=.tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200803-06 (Image-file cd03-06)
  - Pianist Stephen Gosling, performing percussion in Karlheinz Stockhausen's work, Kontakte, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Gosling in Stockhausen Kontakte.tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200803-07 (Image-file cd03-07)
  - Pianist James Avery, with student composer G. Douglas Barrett and percussionist Pascal Pons, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: James Avery G. Douglas Barrett Pascal Pons percussion=.tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200803-08 (Image-file cd03-08)
  - Pianist James Avery with student Tsai-Yun Huang, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: James Avery with student composer Tsai-Yun Huang send.tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200803-09 (Image-file cd03-09)
  - Pianist James Avery with percussionist Pascal Pons rehearsing G. Douglas Barrett's work, Derivation X, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: James Avery, piano Pascal Pons, percusssion.tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200803-10 (Image-file cd03-10)
  - Pianist Stephen Gosling with percussionist Tom Kolor in background rehearsing Karlheinz Stockhasuen's work, Kontakte, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Kontakte by Stockhausen.tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200803-11 (Image-file cd03-11)
  - Percussionist Tom Kolor, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Percussion Tom Kolor.tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200803-12 (Image-file cd03-12)
  - Percussionist Rin Ozaki performing Cort Lippe's work, Music for marimba and computer, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: RIN OSAKI ......tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200803-13 (Image-file cd03-13)
  - Percussionist Rin Ozaki performing Cort Lippe's work, Music for marimba and computer, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: RIN OSAKI JPG ==.tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200803-14 (Image-file cd03-14)
  - Percussionist Rin Ozaki performing Cort Lippe's work, Music for marimba and computer, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: RIN OSAKI in Cort Lippe TIF=.tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200803-15 (Image-file cd03-15)
  - Percussionist Rin Ozaki performing Cort Lippe's work, Music for marimba and computer, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: RIN OSAKI send=-.tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200803-16 (Image-file cd03-16)
  - Percussionist Rin Ozaki performing Cort Lippe's work, Music for marimba and computer, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: RIN OSAKI.tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200803-17 (Image-file cd03-17)
  - Percussionist Rin Ozaki performing Cort Lippe's work, Music for marimba and computer, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Rin Osaki in Cort Lippe TIF.tif (Image-file cd03-18)
  - Percussionist Rin Ozaki performing Cort Lippe's work, Music for marimba and computer, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Rin Osaki in Cort Lippe.tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200803-19 (Image-file cd03-19)
  - Percussionist Rin Ozaki at the marimba, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: send Rin Osaki.tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200803-20 (Image-file cd03-20)
  - Pianist Stephen Gosling and percussionist Tom Kolor performing Karlheinz Stockhausen's work, Kontakte, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Stephen Gosling piano, Tom Koler Percussion in Stockhausen K.tif (Image-file cd03-21)
  - Pianist Stephen Gosling performing Karlheinz Stockhausen's work, Kontakte, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Stephen Gosling, piano playing Stockhausen.tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200803-22 (Image-file cd03-22)
  - Student composer Andrew Colella at computer, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: student composer Andrew Collela at computer.tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200803-23 (Image-file cd03-23)
  - Pianist James Avery and percussionist Pascal Pons performing G. Douglas Barrett's work, Derivation X, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: student composer Barrett piano James Avery percussion Pascal.tif (Image-file cd03-24)
  - Percussionist Pascal Pons rehearsing, with student composer Jonathan Wilkes in background, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: student composer Jonathan Wilkes percussion Pascal Pons.tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200803-25 (Image-file cd03-25)
  - Student composers Kerith Livengood and Jeffrey Trevino, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: studentcomposter Livinggood and Trevino.tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200803-26 (Image-file cd03-26)
  - Percussionist Tom Kolor, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Tom Kolor- Percussion.tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200803-27 (Image-file cd03-27)
  - Student composer Jeffrey Trevino, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Trevino student somposer.tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200803-28 (Image-file cd03-28)
  - Percussionist Tom Kolor, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: xTom Kolor, percussion.tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200803-29 (Image-file cd03-29)
- Roberto Morales, June 2008, IV.; 1 CD-ROM (33 image files in TIFF format)
  - Composer Roberto Morales performing his work, Historia de Culebres, at the piano, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: -Roberto Morales Historia de Culebras.tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200804-01 (Image-file cd04-01)
  - Composer Roberto Morales performing his work, Historia de Culebras, in front of a projected film, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: ====001 Roberto Morales.tif (Image-file cd04-02)
  - Composer Roberto Morales performing his work, Historia de Culebras, in front of a projected film, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: =====Roberto Morales Tif..tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200804-03 (Image-file cd04-03)
  - Pianist Eun-Ju Kim performing Roberto Morales's work, Remembrance, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Eun Ju Kim, piano inRemembrence by Morales.tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200804-04 (Image-file cd04-04)
  - Pianist Eun-Ju Kim performing Roberto Morales's work, Remembrance, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Eun Ju Kim, piano.tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200804-05 (Image-file cd04-05)
  - Pianist Eun-Ju Kim with composer Roberto Morales, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Eun Ju Kim- Roberto Morales composer.tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200804-06 (Image-file cd04-06)
  - Pianist Eun Ju Kim, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Eun Ju Kim.tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200804-07 (Image-file cd04-07)
  - Pianist Eun Ju Kim, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Eun Ju Piano.tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200804-08 (Image-file cd04-08)
  - Pianist Eun Ju Kim, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Eun Ju.tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200804-09 (Image-file cd04-09)
  - Composer Roberto Morales performing his work, Historia de Culebras, in front of a projected film, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Historia de Culebras Robeto Morales.tif (Image-file cd04-10)
  - Composer Roberto Morales, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: JIB 08 001.tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200804-11 (Image-file cd04-11)
  - Conductor James Avery with composer Roberto Morales, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: James Avery, composer Roberto Morales.tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200804-12 (Image-file cd04-12)
  - Pianist Eun Ju Kim, with bassist Sven Kestel and percussionist Tom Kolor, performing Roberto Morales's work, Remembrance, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: music by Roberto Morales Eun Ju piano.jpg In UBdigit as file name: JIB200804-13 (Image-file cd04-13)
  - Pianist Eun Ju Kim, with bassist Sven Kestel and percussionist Tom Kolor, performing Roberto Morales's work, Remembrance, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: music by Roberto Morales Eun Ju piano.tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200804-14 (Image-file cd04-14)
  - James Avery conducting rehearsal of Roberto Morales's work, Remembrance, with Eun Ju Kim, piano, Martina Roth, flute, Sven Kestel, double bass, Tom Kolor (left) and Pascal Pons (right), percussion, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: R.tif (Image-file cd04-15)
  - James Avery conducting rehearsal of Roberto Morales's work, Remembrance, with Eun Ju Kim, piano, Martina Roth, flute, Sven Kestel, double bass, Tom Kolor (center) and Pascal Pons (left), percussion, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: REMEMBRENCE rehearsal 08-.tif (Image-file cd04-16)
  - James Avery conducting rehearsal of Roberto Morales's work, Remembrance, with Eun Ju Kim, piano, Martina Roth, flute, Sven Kestel, double bass, Tom Kolor (center) and Pascal Pons (left), percussion, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: REMEMBRENCE rehearsal 08.tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200804-17 (Image-file cd04-17)
  - Tom Kolor (center), Pascal Pons (left), percussion, Martina Roth, flute, and Sven Kestel, double bass, rehearse Roberto Morales's work, Remembrance, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Rehearsal for Remembrence by Morales.tif (Image-file cd04-18)
  - Pianist Eun Ju Kim and percussionist Tom Kolor rehearse Roberto Morales's work, Remembrance, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: rehearsal Roberto Morales.tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200804-19 (Image-file cd04-19)
  - James Avery conducting rehearsal of Roberto Morales's work, Remembrance, with Eun Ju Kim, piano, Martina Roth, flute, Sven Kestel, double bass, Tom Kolor (left) and Pascal Pons (right), percussion, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Remembrance Roberto Morales.tif (Image-file cd04-20)
  - James Avery conducting rehearsal of Roberto Morales's work, Remembrance, with Eun Ju Kim, piano, Martina Roth, flute, Sven Kestel, double bass, Tom Kolor (center) and Pascal Pons (left), percussion, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Remembrence by Morales-rehearsal.tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200804-21 (Image-file cd04-21)